Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
( Theme music playing )
♪ Game of Thrones 1x04 ♪
Cripples. Bastards. and Broken Things
Original Air Date on May 8. 2011
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
( Bird cawing )
Nan:
The little lord's
been dreaming again.
( Growling )
- We have visitors.
- I don't want to see anyone.
Really?
If I was cooped up all day
with no one but this old bat
for company. I'd go mad.
Anyway. you don't have a choice.
Robb's waiting.
- I don't want to go.
- Neither do I.
But Robb's
Lord of Winterfell.
which means I do what he says.
and you do what I say.
Hodor!
- Hodor?
- Help Bran down the hall.
Hodor.
Tyrion:
I must say I received a slightly
warmer welcome on my last visit.
Robb:
Any man of The Night's Watch
is welcome at Winterfell.
Any man of The Night's Watch.
but not I. eh. boy?
I'm not your boy.
Lannister.
I'm Lord of Winterfell
while my father is away.
- Then you might learn a lord's courtesy.
- ( Door opens )
So it's true.
Hello. Bran.
Do you remember anything
about what happened?
He has no memory
of that day.
- Curious.
- Why are you here
would your charming companion
be so kind as to kneel?
- My neck is beginning to hurt.
- Kneel. Hodor.
- Do you like to ride. Bran?
- Yes.
Well. I mean
I did like to.
- The boy has lost the use of his legs.
- What of it?
With the right horse and saddle.
even a cripple can ride.
- I'm not a cripple.
- Then I'm not a dwarf.
My father will
rejoice to hear it.
I have a gift
for you.
Give that to your saddler.
He'll provide the rest.
You must shape
the horse to the rider.
Start with a yearling
and teach it to respond
to the reins
and to the boy's voice.
Will I really be
able to ride?
You will.
On horseback you will be
as tall as any of them.
Is this some kind of trick?
Why do you want to help him?
I have a tender spot
in my heart
for cripples. bastards
and broken things.
You've done my brother
a kindness.
The hospitality
of Winterfell is yours.
Spare me your false courtesies.
Lord Stark.
There's a brothel
outside your walls.
There I'll find a bed and both
of us can sleep easier.
Couldn't resist
some Northern ass?
If you like redheads.
ask for Ros.
Come to see me off. Greyjoy?
Kind of you.
Your master doesn't seem
to like Lannisters.
- He's not my master.
- No. of course not.
What happened here?
Where is Lady Stark?
Why didn't she receive me?
- She wasn't feeling well.
- She's not in Winterfell. is she?
- Where did she go?
- My Lady's whereabouts--
My Lady?
( Chuckles )
Your loyalty to your captors
is touching.
Tell me. how do you think
balon Greyjoy would feel
if he could see his only
surviving son has turned lackey?
I still remember seeing
my father's fleet
burn in Lannisport.
I believe your uncles
were responsible?
Must have been a pretty sight.
Nothing prettier than watching
sailors burn alive.
Yes. a great victory
for your people.
- Shame how it all turned out.
- We were outnumbered 10 to one--
a stupid rebellion then.
I suppose your father
realized that
when your brothers
died in battle.
Now here you are.
your enemy's squire.
- Careful. imp.
- I've offended you.
Forgive me. it's been
a rough morning.
Anyway. don't despair.
I'm a constant disappointment
to my own father
and I've learned
to live with it.
- ( Coin clinks )
- Your next tumble with Ros is on me.
I'll try not
to wear her out.
( Exhales )
Jon:
Shoulder. legs.
Leg. shoulder. leg.
Left foot forward.
Good.
Now pivot as you
deliver the stroke.
Put all your weight
behind it.
What in seven hells
is that?
Pyp:
They'll need an eighth hell
to fit him in.
( Laughter )
Tell them
your name.
Samwell Tarly.
of Horn Hill--
I mean. I was of Horn Hill.
- I've come to take the black.
- Come to take the black pudding.
( Laughter )
Well. you couldn't be
any worse than you look.
Rast...
See what he can do.
( Yelps )
( Whimpers )
I yield.
- Please. no more.
- On your feet.
Pick up your sword.
Hit him till he
finds his feet.
( Samwell yelping )
( Whimpering )
It seems they've run short of
poachers and thieves down South.
- Now they send us squealing bloody pigs.
- Jon!
- Again. harder.
- ( Snarls )
( Shrieks )
I yield!
Enough!
- ( Samwell sobbing )
- He yielded.
Looks like
the bastard's in love.
All right then.
Lord Snow.
you wish to defend your lady love.
let's make it an exercise.
You two. Three of you ought
to be sufficient
to make
lady piggy squeal.
All you've got to do is
get past the bastard.
- Are you sure you want to do this?
- No.
Yield yield yield!
I yield.
We're done
for today.
Go clean the armory.
That's all
you're good for.
- Well fought!
- Piss off.
( Spits )
Did he hurt you?
I've had worse.
You can call me Sam...
If you want.
- My mother calls me Sam--
- it's not going to get any easier. you know?
You're going to have
to defend yourself.
Why didn't you get up
and fight?
I wanted to.
- I just couldn't.
- Why not?
I'm a coward.
- My father always says so.
- The Wall's no place for cowards.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I just... wanted
to thank you.
A bloody coward.
People saw us
talking to him.
Now they'll think
we're cowards too.
You're too stupid
to be a coward.
- You're too stupid to be a--
- Quick now.
before summer's over.
( Laughing )
C'mere!
( Drums playing )
( Horse neighs )
- ( Neighs )
- Hyah hyah!
Jorah:
Vaes Dothrak--
the city of the horselords.
A pile of mud.
Mud and shit
and twigs--
- best these savages can do.
- These are my people now.
You shouldn't
call them savages.
I'll call them what I like.
because they're my people.
This is my army.
Khal Drogo is marching the
wrong way with my army.
If my brother was given
an army of Dothraki.
could you conquer
the Seven Kingdoms?
The Dothraki have never
crossed the Narrow Sea.
They fear any water
their horses can't drink.
But if they did?
King Robert is fool enough
to meet them in open battle.
but the men
advising him are different.
- And you know these men?
- I fought beside them once.
long ago.
Now Ned Stark wants my head.
He drove me
from my land.
You sold slaves.
Aye.
- Why?
- I had no money
and an expensive wife.
And where is she now?
In another place.
with another man.
- Your Grace?
- Yes. my dear?
They call you
the Last Dragon...
They do.
You have dragon's blood
in your veins?
It's entirely possible.
( Chuckles )
What happened to the dragons?
I was told that brave men
killed them all.
The brave men
didn't kill dragons.
rode them.
Rode them from Valyria
to build the greatest civilization
this world
has ever seen.
The breath
of the greatest dragon
forged the Iron Throne.
which the usurper is
keeping warm for me.
The swords
of the vanquished.
a thousand of them...
Melted together
like so many candles.
I have always wanted
to see a dragon.
There is nothing in the world
that I would rather see.
Really.
Why dragons?
They can fly.
And wherever they are.
just a few flaps of their wings
and they're
somewhere else...
Far away.
And they can kill.
Anyone or anything that
tries to hurt them
- gets burned away to nothing...
- ( Gasps )
...Like so many candles.
Ow.
Yes.
Seeing a dragon
would make me very happy.
Well. after 15 years
in a pleasure house.
I imagine just seeing
the sky makes you happy.
I was not locked in.
I have seen things.
- What have you seen?
- I've seen...
A man from Asshai with a dagger
of real dragonglass.
- Ooh.
- I've seen a man who could
change his face the way that
other men change their clothes.
And I've seen a pirate
who wore his weight in gold
and whose ship had
sails of colored silk.
So...
Have you seen one?
- A pirate ship?
- A dragon.
No.
No. the last one died many years
before I was born.
I'll tell you
what I have seen:
Their skulls.
They used to decorate
the throne room in the Red Keep.
When I was very young.
just three or four.
my father used
to walk me down the rows
and I'd recite
their names for him.
When I got them all right.
he'd give me a sweet.
The ones closest to the door were
the last ones they were able to hatch
and they were all
stunted and wrong.
Skulls no bigger
than dog skulls.
But as you got closer
to the Iron Throne...
They got bigger
and bigger and bigger.
There was Ghiscar
and Valryon.
Vermithrax.
Essovius--
( Gasps )
Archonei.
Meraxes.
Vhagar...
- And Balerion the dread...
- ( Moans )
...Whose fire forged
the Seven Kingdoms
into one.
What happened
to the skulls?
I don't know.
The usurper had them
smashed to powder. I expect.
Scattered to the wind.
That's very sad.
Yes. it is.
What did I buy you for?
- To make me sad?
- No. your Grace.
To. uh. teach your sister.
To teach my sister how
to be a better lover?
You think I bought you to make
Khal Drogo happy?
Oh. you pretty
little idiot.
( Chuckles )
Go on then.
Get on with it.
Someday your husband
will sit there
and you will sit
by his side.
And one day. before too long.
you will present your son to the court.
All the Lords of Westeros
will gather here to see
the little prince--
what if I have a girl?
Gods be good. you'll have boys and girls
and plenty of them.
What if I only
have girls?
I wouldn't worry
about that.
Jeyne Poole's mother had five children--
all of them girls.
Yes. but it's
highly unlikely.
But what if?
Well. if you only
had girls.
I suppose the throne would
pass to Prince Joffrey's little brother.
And everyone
would hate me.
Nobody could ever
hate you.
- Joffrey does.
- Nonsense.
Why would you say
such a thing?
That business with the wolves?
Sansa.
I've told you
a hundred times:
- A direwolf is not--
- please shut up about it.
Do you remember
your lessons?
Who built the Iron Throne?
Aegon the Conqueror.
And who built
the Red Keep?
Maegor the Cruel.
And how many years
did it take to build--
my grandfather and Uncle
were murdered here. weren't they?
They were killed on the orders of
King Aerys. yes.
- The Mad King.
- Commonly known as the Mad King.
Why were they killed?
You should be speak to your
father about these matters.
I don't want to speak
to my father-- ever.
Sansa. you will
find it in your heart
to forgive your father.
No. I won't.
Man:
It's The Hand's
tournament that's causing
- all this trouble. My Lords.
- The King's tournament.
I assure you The Hand
wants no part of it.
Call it what you will.
Lord Stark. Ser.
the city is packed with people
and more flooding in every day.
Last night we had a tavern riot.
a brothel fire.
three stabbings and a drunken horse race
down the Street of Sisters.
- Dreadful.
- If you can't keep the King's peace.
perhaps the city watch should be
commanded by someone who can.
- I need more men.
- Ned: You'll get 50.
- Lord Baelish will see it paid for.
- I will?
You found money
for a champion's purse.
you can find money
to keep the peace.
I'll also give you
20 of my household guard
till the crowds
have left.
Thank you.
My Lord Hand. Ser.
They will be put
to good use.
The sooner this is over.
the better.
The realm prospers
from such events. My Lord.
They give the great
a chance at glory.
and the lowly a respite
from their woes.
Littlefinger:
And every inn in
the city is full
and the whores
are walking bow-legged.
I'm sure the tourney
puts coins in many a pocket.
- Hmmm.
- Now...
If there's nothing else.
My Lords?
Oh. this heat.
On days like this.
I envy you Northerners
your summer snows.
Until tomorrow. My Lord--
I've been hoping to talk
to you about Jon Arryn.
Lord Arryn?
Oh. his death was
a great sadness
to all of us.
I took personal charge
of his care.
but I could not
save him.
His sickness struck him
very hard and very fast.
I saw him in my chambers
just the night
before he passed.
Lord Jon often came
to me for counsel.
Why?
( Offended )
I have been Grand Maester
for many years.
Kings and Hands have come to me
for advice since--
What did Jon want
the night before he died?
Oh. he came inquiring
after a book.
A book?
What book?
Oh. I fear
it would be of little interest
to you. My Lord.
A ponderous Tome.
No. I'd like to read it.
"The Lineages and Histories
of the Great H
of the Seven Kingdoms.
with descriptions
of many high lords
and noble ladies
and their children."
"Harkon Umber.
first of his name.
born to Lord Hother Umber
and Lady Amaryllis Umber
in the 183rd year
after Aegon's landing.
at the last hearth.
Blue of eye. brown of hair
and fair complected.
died in his 14th year
of a wound sustained
in a bear hunt."
As I said. My Lord.
a ponderous read.
Did Jon Arryn tell you
what he wanted with it?
He did not. My Lord.
And I did not presume to ask.
- Jon's death...
- Such a tragedy.
...Did he say anything to you
during his final hours?
Nothing of import.
My Lord.
Oh-- there was one phrase
he kept repeating:
"The seed is strong."
I think it was.
- "The seed is strong"?
- Mm.
- What does that mean?
- Oh.
the dying mind is
a demented mind. Lord Stark.
For all the weight
they're given.
last words are usually
as significant
as first words.
And you're quite certain
he died of a natural illness?
What else could it be?
Poison.
A disturbing thought.
No no no. I don't
think it likely.
The Hand
was loved by all.
What sort of man
would dare--
I've heard it said that poison
is a woman's weapon.
Yes. women.
cravens...
And eunuchs.
Did you know that
Lord Varys is a eunuch?
Everybody knows that.
Yes yes. of course.
How that sort of person
found himself
on the King's Council.
I will never know.
I've taken enough
of your time.
No trouble at all. My Lord.
It's a great honor--
thank you.
I'll find my own way out.
( Footsteps approaching )
Syrio says a water dancer
can stand on one toe
for hours.
It's a hard fall
down these steps.
Syrio says every hurt
is a lesson
and every lesson
makes you better.
- Tomorrow I'm going to be chasing cats.
- Cats?
Syrio says.
He says every swordsman
should study cats.
They're quiet as shadows
and as light as feathers.
You have to be
quick to catch them.
He's right about that.
Now that Bran's awake
will he come
live with us?
Well. he needs to get
his strength back first.
He wants to be
a knight of the Kingsguard.
- He can't be one now. can he?
- No.
But someday
he could be
Lord of a Holdfast
or sit on
the King's Council.
Or he might raise castles
like Brandon the builder.
Can I be Lord
of a Holdfast?
( Chuckles )
You will marry
a high lord
and rule his castle.
And your sons
shall be knights
and princes and lords.
Hmm?
- No.
That's not me.
( Wind gusting )
Hello.
Ser Alliser said I'm to be
your new Watch partner.
I should warn you.
I don't see
all that well.
Come stand by the fire.
- It's warmer.
- No. that's all right. I'm fine.
You're not.
You're freezing.
I don't like
high places.
You can't fight.
You can't see.
You're afraid of heights
and almost everything else probably.
What are you
doing here. Sam?
On the morning of my 18th Nameday.
my father came to me.
"You're almost
a man now." he said...
"But you're not worthy
of my land and title.
Tomorrow. you're going
to take the black.
forsake all claim to your
inheritance and start North.
If you do not."
he said...
"Then we'll have a hunt
and somewhere in these woods
your horse will stumble
and you'll be thrown
from your saddle to die.
Or so I'll tell
your mother.
Nothing would
please me more."
Ser Alliser's going to make me
fight again tomorrow. isn't he?
- Yes. he is.
- ( Moans )
I'm not going to get
any better. you know?
Well...
You can't get any worse.
( Chuckling )
I hear you're reading
a boring book.
Hmph.
Pycelle talks too much.
Oh. he never stops.
Do you know Ser Hugh
of the Vale?
Not surprising.
Until recently.
he was only a squire--
Jon Arryn's squire.
He was knighted
almost immediately
after his master's
untimely death.
Knighted for what?
Why are you
telling me this?
I promised cat
that I'd help you.
Where is Ser Hugh?
- I'll speak to him.
- A singularly bad idea.
Do you see
that boy there?
( Whispers )
One of Varys's little birds.
The spider has taken a great
interest in your comings and goings.
Now look there.
That one belongs
to the Queen.
And do you see that septa
pretending to read her book?
Varys or the Queen?
No. she's one
of mine.
Is there someone in your service
whom you trust completely?
- Yes.
- The wiser answer was no. My Lord.
Get a message to
this paragon of yours--
discreetly--
send him to question Ser Hugh.
After that. you might want him
to visit a certain armorer in the city.
He lives in a large house at the top
of the Street of Steel.
- Why?
- I have my observers. as I said.
and it's possible
that they saw Lord Arryn
visit this armorer several times
in the weeks before his death.
Lord Baelish. perhaps I was
wrong to distrust you.
Distrusting me was
the wisest thing
you've done since you climbed
off your horse.
- ( Hammering )
- ...Two. three.
24. five.
six. 27.
- 28. 29--
- Ser Hugh?
30. 31. 32
- Ser Hugh!
- As you can see. I'm busy.
I'm here on behalf
of Lord Eddard Stark.
the Hand of the King.
I'm the Captain
of his guard.
I'm sorry. I didn't catch
your name. Ser...
No "Ser."
I'm not a knight.
I see. Well. it just
so happens that I am.
( Continues counting )
Jory:
He said he'd be glad
to talk to the hand himself.
He's a knight.
you see.
Ah. a knight.
They strut around
like roosters down here.
Even the ones who've never seen
an arrow coming their way.
You shouldn't be
out here. My Lord.
- There's no telling who has eyes where.
- Let them look.
The former Hand did call on me.
My Lord. several times.
I regret to say he did not honor me
with his patronage.
What did
Lord Arryn want?
He always came to see the boy.
I'd like to see him
as well.
As you Gendry! My lord.
Here he is.
Strong for his age.
He works hard.
Show the hand
the helmet you made. lad.
- This is fine work.
- It's not for sale.
Boy. this is
the King's Hand!
- If his lordship wants the helm--
- I made it for me.
- Forgive him. My Lord.
- There's nothing to forgive.
When Lord Arryn came to visit you.
what would you talk about?
He just asked me questions
is all. My Lord.
What kind
of questions?
About my work at first.
if I was being treated well.
if I liked it here.
But then he started
asking me about my mother.
- Your mother?
- Who she was. what she looked like.
What did you tell him?
She died when I was little.
She had yellow hair.
She'd sing to me sometimes.
Look at me.
Get back to work. lad.
If the day ever comes
when that boy
would rather wield
a sword than forge one.
you send him to me.
( Hammer banging )
Find anything?
King Robert's
bastard son.
( Robert laughing )
- Woman: He likes that.
- ( Women laughing )
This is for the King
from Lord Stark.
- ( Robert laughs )
- Should I leave it with--
shhh.
Listen.
Do you hear them?
How many do you think
are in there with him?
Huh?
- Guess.
- Three?
- ( Laughter )
- Four.
He likes to do this
when I'm on duty--
he makes me listen
as he insults my sister.
- ( Door opens )
- ( Laughter )
Forgive me. My Lord--
Why do I have to forgive you?
Have you wronged me?
We've met before. you know.
Have we?
Strange. I've forgotten.
The siege of Pyke.
We fought side by side one afternoon.
Ah.
- That's where you got your scar?
- Aye.
Oh.
One of the Greyjoys
nearly took my eye.
- Vicious sons of whores.
- They like their bloodshed.
They stopped liking it
at the end.
That was a proper battle.
Do you remember
Thoros of Myr charging
through the breach?
With his burning sword?
I'll remember that
till the day I die.
I saw the youngest of the
Greyjoy lads at Winterfell.
It was like seeing a shark
on a mountaintop.
Theon?
He's a good lad.
I doubt it.
- ( Laughter )
- ( Door opens )
Robert:
I'll bet you smell
of blackberry jam!
Let me smell it.
Come here.
Can I leave this
with you?
The message
from Lord Stark.
I don't serve Lord Stark.
( Laughter continues )
- Where have you been?
- Watch duty.
- With Sam.
- Ah. prince porkchop.
- Where is he?
- He wasn't hungry.
- Impossible!
- ( Chuckles )
That's enough.
Sam's no different
from the rest of us.
There was no place
for him in the world.
so he's come here.
We're not going to hurt him
in the training yard anymore.
Never again.
no matter what Thorne says.
He's our brother now
and we're going to protect him.
Rast:
You are in love. Lord Snow.
( Laughter )
You girls can do
as you please.
But if Thorne puts me
up against lady piggy.
I'm gonna slice me off
a side of bacon.
( Laughter )
( Snoring )
- ( Panting )
- ( Growling )
No one touches Sam.
( Snarls )
( Growling continues )
What are you
waiting for?
Attack him!
You get in there.
( Softly )
Hit me.
Go on. hit me!
( Shouts )
- I yield!
- ( Laughter )
Yield yield.
I yield.
You think this
is funny. do you?
When you're out there
beyond The Wall
with the sun going down.
do you want
a man at your back?
Or a sniveling boy?
( Sobbing )
You send this whore
to give me commands?
I should have sent
you back her head!
Forgive me. Khaleesi.
I did as you asked.
Hush now.
It's all right.
- Irri. take her and leave us.
- Yes. Khaleesi.
- Why did you hit her?!
- How many times do I have to tell you?
You do not command me.
I wasn't commanding you.
I just wanted to invite
you to supper.
- What's this?
- It's a gift.
- I had it made for you.
- Dothraki rags?
- Are you going to dress me now?
- Please.
This stinks of manure.
All of it.
( Gasps ) Stop-- stop it.
You would turn me into one
of them. wouldn't you?
Next you'll want
to braid my hair.
You've no right
to a braid.
You've won
no victories yet.
You do not
talk back to me!
You are a horselord's slut.
And now you've woken
the dragon--
- ( metal jangles )
- ( Screams )
I am a Khaleesi
of the Dothraki!
I am the wife
of the great Khal
and I carry his son
inside me.
The next time
you raise a hand to me
will be the last time
you have hands.
( Thunder rumbles.
rain pattering )
I know for a fact
that some of the officers
go to that brothel
in mole's town.
I wouldn't doubt it.
Don't you think it's
a little bit unfair?
Making us take our vows
while they sneak off
for a little
sally on the side?
- Sally on the side?
- It's silly. isn't it?
What. we can't defend
the wall unless we're celibate?
It's absurd.
I didn't think you'd be
so upset about it.
Why not?
- Because I'm fat?
- No.
But I like girls just
as much as you do.
They might not
like me as much.
I've never--
been with one.
You've probably
had hundreds.
No.
As a matter of fact.
I'm the same as you.
( Scoffs )
Yeah.
I find that hard
to believe.
I came very close once.
I was alone in a room
with a naked girl. but--
you didn't know
where to put it?
I know where to put it.
Was she...
Old and ugly?
Young and gorgeous.
A whore named Ros.
What color hair?
- Red.
- Oh. I like red hair.
And her. um...
Her...
- You don't want to know.
- That good?
- Better.
- Oh no.
So why exactly
did you not make love
to Ros with the perfect--?
What's my name?
Jon Snow?
And why is
my surname snow?
Because...
You're a bastard
from the North.
I never met my mother.
My father wouldn't even
tell me her name.
I don't know if she's
living or dead.
I don't know
if she's a noblewoman
or a Fisherman's wife...
Or a whore.
So I sat there
in the brothel as Ros
took off her clothes.
But I couldn't do it.
Because all I could
think was
what if I got her pregnant
and she had a child.
another bastard named Snow?
It's not a good life
for a child.
Ah. mmm.
So...
You didn't know
where to put it?
( Laughing )
Enjoying yourselves?
You look cold. boys.
( Door creaks )
It is a bit nippy.
A bit nippy.
yeah. by the fire.
indoors.
It's still summer.
Do you boys even remember
the last winter?
How long has it been now?
What. 10 years?
I remember.
Was it uncomfortable
at Winterfell?
Were there days when
you just couldn't get warm.
never mind how many fires
your servants built?
- I build my own fires.
- That's admirable.
I spent six months out there.
beyond The Wall
during the last winter.
It was supposed to be
a two-week mission.
We heard a rumor Mance Rayder
was planning to attack Eastwatch.
So we went out to look
for some of his men--
capture them.
gather some knowledge.
The Wildlings who fight
for Mance Rayder are hard men.
Harder than you'll ever be.
They know their country
better than we do.
They knew there was
a storm coming in.
So they hid in their caves
and waited for it to pass.
And we got caught
in the open.
Wind so strong
it yanked 100-foot trees
straight from the ground.
roots and all.
If you took your gloves off
to find your cock
to have a piss.
you lost a finger
to the frost.
And all in darkness.
You don't know cold.
Neither of you do.
The horses died first.
We didn't have enough to feed them.
to keep them warm.
Eating the horses was easy.
But later when we
started to fall...
That wasn't easy.
We should have had a couple of
boys like you along. shouldn't we?
- ( Grabs )
- ( Gasps )
Soft. fat boys like you.
We'd have lasted
a fortnight on you
and still had bones
leftover for soup.
Soon we'll have
new recruits
and you lot will be passed along
to the Lord Commander
for assignment
and they will call you
men of The Night's Watch.
but you'd be fools
to believe it.
You're boys still.
And come the winter
you will die...
Like flies.
I hit him.
I hit the dragon.
Your brother Rhaegar
was the Last Dragon.
Viserys is less than
the shadow of a snake.
He is still
the true king.
The truth now:
Do you want to see your brother
sitting on the Iron Throne?
No.
But the common people
are waiting for him.
Illyrio said they are sewing dragon
banners and praying for his return.
The common people pray for rain.
health and a summer that never ends.
They don't care what games
the high lords play.
What do you pray for.
Ser Jorah?
Home.
I pray for home too.
My brother will never take back
the Seven Kingdoms.
He couldn't lead an army
even if my husband gave him one.
He'll never take us home.
( Crowd chattering )
Lover's quarrel?
I'm sorry.
Do I...?
Sansa dear. this is Lord Baelish.
He's known--
an old friend
of the family.
I've known your mother
a long long time.
- Why do they call you Littlefinger?
- Arya!
- Don't be rude!
- No. it's quite all right.
When I was a child
I was very small
and I come from a little spit of land
called The Fingers.
so you see.
it's an exceedingly
clever nickname.
I've been sitting here
for days!
Start the damn joust
before I piss myself!
( Cheering )
Gods. who is that?
Littlefinger:
Ser Gregor Clegane.
They call him the Mountain.
The hound's older brother.
- And his opponent?
- Littlefinger: Ser Hugh of the Vale.
He was
Jon Arryn's squire.
Lo how far he's come.
Yes yes. enough
of the bloody pomp.
Have at it!
( Horse neighs )
( Screams )
( Crowd gasps )
( Gurgling )
Not what you
were expecting?
Has anyone ever told you the story
of the Mountain and the Hound?
Lovely little tale
of brotherly love.
The Hound was just a pup.
six years old maybe.
Gregor a few years older--
already a big lad. already
getting a bit of a reputation.
Some lucky boys
just born with a talent
for violence.
One evening Gregor found
his little brother
playing with a toy
by the fire--
Gregor's toy.
a wooden knight.
Gregor never said a word.
he just grabbed his brother
by the scruff of his neck
and shoved his face
into the burning coals.
Held him there
while the boy screamed.
while his face melted.
There aren't very many people
who know that story.
I won't tell anyone.
I promise.
No. please don't.
If the Hound so much as
heard you mention it.
I'm afraid all the knights
in King's Landing
would not be able
to save you.
( Knocks )
My Lord.
her Grace the Queen.
- Your Grace.
- You're missing your tournament.
Putting my name on it
doesn't make it mine.
I thought we might put what happened
on the Kingsroad behind us--
the ugliness
with the wolves.
And forcing you to kill
the beast was extreme.
Though sometimes we go to extremes
where our children are concerned.
How is Sansa?
She likes it here.
She's the only
Stark who does.
Favors her mother.
not much
of the North in her.
- What are you doing here?
- I might ask the same of you.
What is it you
hope to accomplish?
The King called on me
to serve him and the realm.
and that's what I'll do
until he tells me otherwise.
You can't change him.
You can't help him.
He'll do what he wants. which is
all he's ever done.
You'll try your best
to pick up the pieces.
If that's my job.
then so be it.
You're just a soldier.
aren't you?
You take your orders
and you carry on.
I suppose it makes sense.
Your older brother was trained to
lead and you were trained to follow.
I was also trained to kill
my enemies. your Grace.
As was I.
( Door opens. closes )
( Horse snorts )
( Dog barking )
Seven blessings to you.
goodfolk!
And to you.
Boy!
Bread. meat and beer. Quickly.
Ah. good idea. grandfather.
I'm starving.
A song
while we wait or--?
I'd rather throw myself
down a well.
Now now. grandfather. this may be your
last chance if you're heading North.
The only music the Northerners know is
the howling of wolves!
- ( Laughs )
- ( Door opens )
Gods.
I'm sorry. My Lord.
We're full up.
- Every room.
- Tyrion: My men can sleep in the stable.
As for myself. I don't
require a large room.
Truly. My Lord.
we have nothing.
Is there nothing I can do...
- ( Coin clanks )
- ...To remedy this?
You can have my room.
Now there's
a clever man.
You can manage food. I trust?
Yoren. dine with me.
- Aye. My Lord.
- My Lord of Lannister!
Might I entertain you
while you eat?
I can sing of your father's victory
at King's Landing!
Nothing would more likely
ruin my supper.
Lady Stark!
What an unexpected
pleasure.
I was sorry to have
missed you at Winterfell.
Lady Stark!
I was still Catelyn Tully
the last time
I stayed here.
You. Ser.
is that the black bat of Harrenhal
I see embroidered on your coat?
It is. My Lady.
And is Lady Whent
a true and honest friend
to my father. Lord Hoster Tully
of Riverrun?
She is.
The red stallion was always
a welcome sight at Riverrun.
My father counts
Jonas Bracken
amongst his oldest
and most loyal bannermen.
Our lord is honored
by his trust.
I envy your father
all his fine friends.
Lady Stark.
but I don't quite see
the purpose of this.
I know your sigil as well--
the Twin Towers
of Frey.
How fares your lord. Ser?
Lord Walder is well.
My Lady.
He has asked your father
for the honor of his presence
on his 90th Nameday.
- He plans to take another wife.
- ( Scoffs )
This man
came into my house
as a guest
and there conspired
to murder my son.
a boy of 10.
In the name of King Robert
and the good lords you serve.
I call upon you
to seize him
and help me return him
to Winterfell
to await the King's Justice.
( Theme music playing )
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm